"use strict";

const { Word } = require("../models");

module.exports = {
  async up(queryInterface, Sequelize) {
    const data = [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: "はい。",
        choice1: "Please",
        choice2: "Thank you",
        choice3: "You are welcome",
        choice4: "Yes",
        correct_answer: "Yes",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: "いいえ",
        choice1: "Please",
        choice2: "No",
        choice3: "You are welcome",
        choice4: "Yes",
        correct_answer: "No",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: "おねがいします。",
        choice1: "Please",
        choice2: "Yes",
        choice3: "You are welcome",
        choice4: "No",
        correct_answer: "Please",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: "ありがとう。",
        choice1: "No",
        choice2: "Yes",
        choice3: "Thank you",
        choice4: "You are welcome",
        correct_answer: "Thank you",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: "どういたしまして。",
        choice1: "No",
        choice2: "You are welcome",
        choice3: "Thank you",
        choice4: "Yes",
        correct_answer: "You are welcome",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: "すみません",
        choice1: "Excuse me",
        choice2: "Refill, please",
        choice3: "How much is this?",
        choice4: "Water please",
        correct_answer: "Excuse me",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: "これください",
        choice1: "Water please",
        choice2: "Refill, please",
        choice3: "This one please",
        choice4: "How much is this?",
        correct_answer: "This one please",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: "いくらですか",
        choice1: "Water please",
        choice2: "How much is this?",
        choice3: "This one please",
        choice4: "Refill, please",
        correct_answer: "How much is this?",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: "お水ください",
        choice1: "Refill, please",
        choice2: "How much is this?",
        choice3: "This one please",
        choice4: "Water please",
        correct_answer: "Water please",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: "大盛りお願いします",
        choice1: "Refill, please",
        choice2: "I'd like a large portion",
        choice3: "This one please",
        choice4: "How much is this?",
        correct_answer: "I'd like a large portion",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: "はい。",
        choice1: "Please",
        choice2: "Thank you",
        choice3: "You are welcome",
        choice4: "Yes",
        correct_answer: "Yes",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: "いいえ",
        choice1: "Please",
        choice2: "No",
        choice3: "You are welcome",
        choice4: "Yes",
        correct_answer: "No",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        question: "おねがいします。",
        choice1: "No",
        choice2: "Yes",
        choice3: "Please",
        choice4: "You are welcome",
        correct_answer: "Please",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: "ありがとう。",
        choice1: "Thank you",
        choice2: "Yes",
        choice3: "You are welcome",
        choice4: "No",
        correct_answer: "Thank you",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: "どういたしまして。",
        choice1: "You are welcome",
        choice2: "Yes",
        choice3: "Thank you",
        choice4: "No",
        correct_answer: "You are welcome",
        createdAt: new Date(),
        updatedAt: new Date(),
      },
    ];

    await Word.bulkCreate(data, {
      updateOnDuplicate: Object.keys(Word.getAttributes()),
    });
  },

  async down(queryInterface, Sequelize) {
    await queryInterface.bulkDelete("words", null, {});
  },
};
